(Amy:)...to use the clinical term, bitchiness...
(Amy:)...is because your mother
isn't making you a priority?
No. Or to use the clinical term: Nuh-uh.
(Amy:)Are you sure?
The infant-mother pair-bond...
(Amy:)...is the building block
of primate psychology.
(Sheldon:)Oh, there it is. It always comes back
to monkeys with you.
(Sheldon:)Just monkeys, monkeys, monkeys.
(Amy:)Sheldon, we're all animals.
(Amy:)There are aspects of you
that are extraordinary...
...but when it comes to relationships,
you're like everybody else.
(Sheldon:)Are you trying to suggest
that my emotional problems...
(Sheldon:)...are no different
than those of a stupid person?
(Amy:)Actually, some research indicates
that by not overthinking...
(Amy:)...the less intelligent
handle emotions better.
(Amy:)Sure you're not coming down
with a cold?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes, the common cold.
Just like everyone else.
(Sheldon:)You'd love that, wouldn't you?
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, this one's sweet.
(Mrs Cooper:)You know, for your rosary rattlers.